(Sheldon:)Your argument is lacking
in all scientific merit.
And it is well-established...
(Sheldon:)...Superman cleans his uniform
by flying into Earth's yellow sun...
(Sheldon:)...which incinerates
any contaminant matter...
(Sheldon:)...and leaves the invulnerable Kryptonian
fabric unharmed and daisy fresh.
(Howard:)What if he gets something
Kryptonian on it?
- Like what?
- I don't know. Kryptonian mustard.
I think we can assume all Kryptonian
condiments were destroyed...
(Sheldon:)...when the planet Krypton exploded.
(Raj:)Or it turned into mustard Kryptonite.
(Raj:)The only way to destroy a rogue
Kryptonian hot dog threatening Earth.
(Leonard:)Raj, please, let's stay serious here.
(Leonard:)Superman's body is Kryptonian,
therefore his sweat is Kryptonian.
(Howard:)Yeah, what about Kryptonian pit stains?
(Sheldon:)Superman doesn't sweat on Earth.
(Howard:)Okay. He's invited for dinner
in the bottle city of Kandor.
(Howard:)He miniaturizes himself, enters the city,
where he loses his super-powers.
(Howard:)Before dinner, his host says,
"Who's up for Kryptonian tetherball?"
Superman works up a sweat, comes back
to Earth, his uniform now stained...